<resources>
    <string name="app_name">inMarket</string>
    <string name="title_screen">Indeed Gambling</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_defaultMessage">Hello, Organizer!</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_SubMessage">What would you like to do today?</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_Browse_text">Browse Events</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_UpcomingText">Upcoming</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_HistoryText">History</string>
    <string name="organizer_home_BrowseText">Browse Events</string>
    <string name="organizer_HomeButton"><![CDATA[< Home]]></string>
    <string-array name="user_roles">
        <item>Entrant</item>
        <item>Organizer</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="Guidelines_for_Entrant">
1. Ensure your profile information (name, email, phone) is accurate and up to date. This is how organizers will contact you.\n\n
2. You may only join the waiting list once per event. Duplicate entries will be removed to ensure fairness.\n\n
3. Joining a waiting list does not guarantee selection. Entrants are randomly chosen after the registration period ends.\n\n
4. If you are selected ("win" the lottery), confirm or decline your spot promptly to allow others a fair chance.\n\n
5. Enable notifications in your profile view to stay informed about event results and updates.\n\n
6. Respect event rules, organizers, and other entrants. Harassment or misuse of the app will result in removal.\n\n
7. If you need to cancel or update your participation, do so as soon as possible.\n\n
8. Always verify event details, such as time and location, before attending.\n\n
9. Participate responsibly and enjoy the community events fairly!
</string>
    <string name="Guidelines_for_Organizer">
   1. Ensure all event details (name, description, location) are accurate and up to date. This information is visible to all entrants.\n\n
   2. Set clear criteria and requirements for your events. Entrants should understand what is expected.\n\n
   3. Monitor registration periods closely. You can manually end registration early if needed.\n\n
   4. Use the waiting list system fairly.\n\n
   5. Invite entrants from the waiting list when spots become available. \n\n
   6. Track accepted, invited, and cancelled entrants through their respective lists for proper management.\n\n
   7. Export participant lists to CSV for record-keeping and event check-in.\n\n
   8. Send notifications to keep entrants informed about event updates or changes..\n\n
   9. Maintain professionalism and fairness.\n\n
   10. Verify all event logistics (time, location, capacity) before the event date to ensure smooth execution.
    </string>

    <string-array name="profile_filters">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Entrant</item>
        <item>Organizer</item>
        <item>Admin</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>